(Raj:)He said he couldn't afford
to send me money anymore
(Raj:)because of
his active social life.
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)What does that mean,
"active social life"?
(Raj:)Well, let's not talk about him
(Raj:)or whatever shenanigans
he may or may not be up to.
(Raj:)Let's talk about you.
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)Rajesh, is your father
seeing someone?
(Raj:)All I know, Mummy, is that
(Raj:)he's a single wealthy doctor,
and now, for some reason,
(Raj:)there's no money
for your little boy.
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)Well, however much money
your father was giving you,
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)I'll give you more.
Thank you, Mummy, I love you!
(quietly):
Helicopters for everybody!
(Penny:)What's taking so long?
LEONARD: I don't think
this is gonna work.
(Penny:)Just let me see.
(Penny:)Sweetie, you know
you're supposed to wear clothes
(Penny:)underneath a graduation gown.
A: surprised you know that.
B: I wanted to look like
a sexy graduate for you.